export const PASSAGE =
  "In recent years, there has been a growing concern about the impact of plastic pollution on the environment. Plastic waste, especially single-use plastics like bottles and bags, poses a significant threat to marine life and ecosystems. As plastics break down into smaller particles, they enter the food chain, potentially harming animals and even humans. Governments and environmental organizations worldwide are implementing measures to reduce plastic consumption and promote recycling. However, addressing this issue requires collective efforts from individuals, businesses, and policymakers. Consumers can contribute by choosing reusable alternatives and properly disposing of plastic waste. One promising solution is the development of biodegradable plastics, which break down more quickly than traditional plastics, reducing their environmental impact. Additionally, innovations in waste management technologies offer hope for more efficient recycling and disposal methods. As awareness of the plastic pollution problem grows, it is crucial for communities to work together to find sustainable solutions that protect the planet for future generations.";
export const QUESTIONS = {
  1: [
    {
      id: 1,
      question: "What is the main concern addressed in the passage?",
      options: [
        "Climate change",
        "Plastic pollution",
        "Deforestation",
        "Water scarcity",
      ],
      answer: "Plastic pollution",
    },
    {
      id: 2,
      question: "Which type of plastics are mentioned as particularly harmful?",
      options: [
        "Biodegradable plastics",
        "Recyclable plastics",
        "Single-use plastics",
        "Compostable plastics",
      ],
      answer: "Single-use plastics",
    },
    {
      id: 3,
      question:
        "What do governments and environmental organizations aim to achieve?",
      options: [
        "Increase plastic production",
        "Encourage plastic consumption",
        "Reduce plastic consumption",
        "Ban all plastic products",
      ],
      answer: "Reduce plastic consumption",
    },
    {
      id: 4,
      question: "What role can consumers play in addressing plastic pollution?",
      options: [
        "Increasing plastic use",
        "Choosing reusable alternatives",
        "Disposing plastic waste irresponsibly",
        "Ignoring the issue",
      ],
      answer: "Choosing reusable alternatives",
    },
    {
      id: 5,
      question:
        "What is mentioned as a potential solution to the plastic pollution problem?",
      options: [
        "Development of biodegradable plastics",
        "Ignoring waste management technologies",
        "Decreased recycling efforts",
        "Increased plastic production",
      ],
      answer: "Development of biodegradable plastics",
    },
  ],
  2: [
    {
      id: 1,
      question: "How did Hafiz Mian greet the visitor?",
      options: [
        "Good morning",
        "As Salaam Alaikum",
        "Alaikum As Salaam",
        "Adaab",
      ],
      answer: "As Salaam Alaikum",
    },
    {
      id: 2,
      question: "How did the young man look?",
      options: ["Dark", "Wheatish", "Dusky", "Fair"],
      answer: "Fair",
    },
    {
      id: 3,
      question: "What was the visitor wearing",
      options: [
        "Fez cap and kurta",
        "Cap and achkan",
        "Fez cap and achkan",
        "Fez cap and shirt",
      ],
      answer: "Fez cap and achkan",
    },
    {
      id: 4,
      question:
        "What material was the visitor weraing and what was he carrying respectively?",
      options: ["Silk, wool", "Cotton, wool", "Wool, cotton", "Wool, silk"],
      answer: "Silk, wool",
    },
  ],
  3: [
    {
      id: 1,
      question: "Who developed World War II radar technology?",
      options: [
        "Albert Einstein",
        "Thomas Edison",
        "Percy Spencer",
        "Nikola Tesla",
      ],
      answer: "Percy Spencer",
    },
    {
      id: 2,
      question:
        "What was the first surprising application of the magnetron observed by Percy Spencer?",
      options: [
        "Melting a candy bar",
        "Boiling water",
        "Cooking a steak",
        "Toasting bread",
      ],
      answer: "Melting a candy bar",
    },
    {
      id: 3,
      question:
        "What device produced high-intensity microwaves during World War II?",
      options: ["Radar dish", "Magnetron", "Oscilloscope", "Transistor"],
      answer: "Magnetron",
    },
    {
      id: 4,
      question:
        "What year did Percy Spencer make his accidental discovery with the magnetron?",
      options: ["1939", "1941", "1943", "1945"],
      answer: "1945",
    },
    {
      id: 5,
      question:
        "Which food item did not respond well and exploded when exposed to the magnetron?",
      options: ["Candy bar", "Popcorn", "Egg", "Bread"],
      answer: "Egg",
    },
    {
      id: 6,
      question:
        "What was the main function of the magnetron during World War II before its application in cooking?",
      options: [
        "Heating food",
        "Reflecting microwaves off planes to detect them",
        "Broadcasting radio signals",
        "Generating electricity",
      ],
      answer: "Reflecting microwaves off planes to detect them",
    },
  ],
};
